Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1894-1942
  - 1937-1940. Constituent mail filed under name of correspondent and unsorted within each letter of the alphabet
    - Wi-Z publications (Box 139., Folder 1-8)
  - 1938-1940, unsorted (Folder 140.)
    - Conscription (Folder 1-7)
    - Conscription (Box 141., Folder 1-6)
    - Conscription (Box 142., Folder 1-5)
    - Conscription (Box 143., Folder 1-3)
    - Neutrality (Folder 4)
    - Neutrality (Box 144., Folder 1-6)
  - 1938-1940. Unsorted correspondence on the subjects of United States neutrality, conscription, and repeal of the 1937 embargo to discourage sale of arms to Spain during the Spanish Civil War. The letters, post cards and telegrams are usually, but not always, on just one of the subjects listed above (Box 145-162.)
  - 1939-1940. Unsorted constituent mail filed by last name or name of organization
    - A (Box 163., Folder 1)
    - B (Folder 2)
    - Burke-Wadsworth bill (Folder 3)
    - C (Folder 4)
    - D (Folder 5)
    - E (Folder 6)
    - F (Folder 7)
    - G (Folder 8)
    - H (Folder 9)
    - I (Folder 10)
    - J (Folder 11)
    - K (Box 164., Folder 1)
    - L (Folder 2)
    - M (Folder 3)
    - N (Folder 4)
    - O (Folder 5)
    - P (Folder 6)
    - Q (Folder 7)
    - R (Folder 8)
    - S (Box 165., Folder 1)
    - T (Folder 2)
    - U (Folder 3)
    - V (Folder 4)
    - W (Folder 5)
    - Wheeler-Lee bill (Folder 6)
    - Y-Z (Folder 7)
    - Requests for Senator Lundeen's speech "Six Men and War" (Folder 8)
  - 1897-1942. Constituent mail, invitations to speak, bills and receipts, family and personal mail and subscriptions, filed chronologically and alphabetically
    - General
      - Undated (Box 166., Folder 1)
      - 1897-1915 (Folder 2)
      - 1916 (Folder 3)
      - 1917 (Folder 4)
      - 1918 (Folder 5)
      - 1919 (Folder 6)
      - 1920 (Folder 7)
      - 1921 (Folder 8)
      - 1922 (Box 167., Folder 1)
      - 1923 (Folder 2)
      - 1924 (Folder 3)
      - 1925 (Folder 4)
      - 1926 (Folder 5)
      - 1927 (Folder 6)
      - 1928 (Folder 7)
      - 1929 (Box 168., Folder 1)
      - 1930 (Folder 2-3)
      - 1931 (Folder 4)
      - 1933 (Folder 5)
      - 1934 (Folder 6)
      - 1935 (Box 169., Folder 1)
      - 1936 (Folder 2)
      - 1937 (Folder 3-6)
      - 1938 (Folder 7)
      - 1938 (Box 170., Folder 1-5)
      - 1939 (Box 171., Folder 1-6)
      - 1939 (Box 172., Folder 1)
      - 1940 (Folder 2-4)
      - 1941 (Folder 5)
    - Lundeen family
      - Carlson, Otto, Mrs. (Tillie Lundeen) (Box 173., Folder 1)
      - Lagergren, C. J., Mrs. (Folder 2)
      - Lundeen, David and Florence (Folder 3)
      - Lundeen, Ernest and Norma
      - Undated (Folder 4)
      - 1917 (Folder 5)
      - 1918 (Folder 6)
      - 1919 (Folder 7)
      - 1920 (Folder 8)
      - 1921 (Box 174., Folder 1)
      - 1922 (Folder 2)
      - 1923 (Folder 3)
      - 1924 (Folder 4)
      - 1925 (Folder 5)
      - 1926 (Folder 6)
      - 1927 (Folder 7)
      - 1928 (Folder 8)
      - 1930-1931 (Folder 9)
      - 1932 (Folder 10)
      - 1933 (Folder 11)
      - 1934 (Box 175., Folder 1)
      - 1935-1937 (Folder 2)
      - 1938-1940 (Folder 3)
      - Lundeen, Joel and Esther (Folder 4)
      - Lundeen, Mamie (Folder 5)
      - Lundin, C. H. (Folder 6)
      - Lundin, C. H. (Box 176., Folder 1)
      - Lundin, C. H., Mrs. (Folder 2)
      - Samuels, Anna Marie Lundeen (Folder 3)
      - Widen, Ed and Esther Lundeen (Folder 4)
    - Individuals
      - List of correspondents (Box 177., Folder 1)
      - Arens, Henry (Folder 2)
      - Barnett, Fred (Folder 3)
      - Brown, W. Gertrude (Folder 4)
      - Buchheit, J. F. (Folder 5)
      - Chase, Ray P. (Folder 6)
      - Cravens, Fay (Folder 7)
      - Davis, Charles R. (Folder 8)
      - Davis, Tom (Folder 9)
      - Elliot, Henry W. (Folder 10)
      - Fritsche, Louis Albert (Folder 11)
      - Hormel, Jay C. (Folder 12)
      - Hutchinson, Mamie F. (Folder 13-14)
      - Keller, Mildred C. (Folder 15)
      - Kotasek, Rose M. (Folder 16)
      - Lindskoog, Frank (Folder 17)
      - Lundeen, Leonard (Folder 18)
      - McCarter, Cora B. (Box 178., Folder 1)
      - McLean, Edwin L. (Folder 2)
      - Magnant, Solange (Folder 3)
      - Main, Sarah and Nellie (Folder 4)
      - Martin, Lewis Ward (Folder 5)
      - Miller, Emma (Folder 6-8)
      - Moe, Henry Allen (Folder 9)
      - Morrill, Lowell L. (Folder 10)
      - Newton, Walter H. (Folder 11)
      - Oldroyd, O. H. (Folder 12)
      - Ramee, Per (Folder 13)
      - Rifenberg, Jannett (Box 179., Folder 1)
      - Rost, Ernest C. (Folder 2)
      - Solow, Herbert (Folder 3)
      - Stoecher, August (Folder 4)
      - Thompson, William Hale (Folder 5)
      - Van Lear, Thomas (Folder 6)
      - Viereck, George S. (Folder 7-9)
  - 1924-1940. Personal finances (debts paid); constituent mail, arranged alphabetically
    - A unsorted (Box 180., Folder 1)
    - Accounts paid, 1924-1936 (Folder 2)
    - Accounts paid, closed, 1937 (Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Charles A. (Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Doretta (Folder 5)
    - Anderson Motor Company (Folder 6)
    - Andrews Florist (Folder 7)
    - Auto insurance (Folder 8)
    - Awes, M. Sigbert (Folder 9)
    - Ayrlawn Farms (Folder 10)
    - B unsorted (Folder 11)
    - Baker, A. T. (Folder 12)
    - Battery Park Market (Folder 13)
    - La Belle Safety Storage and Moving (Folder 14)
    - Best and Company (Folder 15)
    - Books, World War (Folder 16)
    - Boyd Transfer and Storage Company (Folder 17)
    - Bresky, Eleanor (Folder 18)
    - Budgets
      - 1934-1937 (Folder 19)
      - 1938 (Folder 20)
      - 1939 (Folder 21)
    - C unsorted (Box 181., Folder 1)
    - Campbell Machine Company (Folder 2)
    - Capitol Drug Company (Folder 3)
    - Carleton College (Folder 4)
    - Chapman, Graham (Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Company (Folder 6)
    - Chrysler car (Folder 7)
    - Cohen's (Folder 8)
    - Collier and Son (Folder 9)
    - Committee on Accounts, U.S. House of Representatives (Folder 10)
    - Congressional Club (Folder 11)
    - Cooperative Oil Association (Folder 12)
    - Crume, George P. (Folder 13)
    - D unsorted (Folder 14)
    - Demeules Brothers Wire and Iron Works (Folder 15)
    - Dictograph Products Company (Folder 16)
    - Disabled American Veterans (Folder 17)
    - Dotas, Charles (Folder 18)
    - Drouth relief, 1936, 1937 (Folder 19)
    - Drum, Mrs. Walter (Hattie) (Folder 20)
    - Dues, 1927-1938 (Folder 21)
    - Duluth, Minnesota (Folder 22)
    - Duncan, Clyde A. (Folder 23)
    - Durand, Robert (Folder 24)
    - Durrell, Harvey (Folder 25)
    - Duryea, D. G. (Folder 26)
    - Dvorak, Frank (Folder 27)
    - E unsorted (Folder 28)
    - Edwards, Alyce (Folder 29)
    - Edwards, William Wright (Folder 30)
    - Egekvist Bakeries (Folder 31)
    - Eidman, Mildred G. (Folder 32)
    - Eidness, Rena (Box 182., Folder 1)
    - Eitel, George, Mrs. (Folder 2)
    - Ekwall, Carl (Folder 3)
    - Elafros, John T. (Folder 4)
    - Engagements not accepted (Folder 5)
    - Engstrand, Darwin (Folder 6)
    - Engstrom, E. W. (Folder 7)
    - Engwall, Catherine (Folder 8)
    - Erickson, B. E. (Folder 9)
    - Erickson, E. W., Mrs. (Folder 10)
    - Erickson, Leslie (Folder 11)
    - Ericksson, Leonard (Folder 12)
    - Ervin, William S. (Folder 13)
    - Evanoff, Tashko (Folder 14)
    - F unsorted (Folder 15)
    - Fairley, John D. (Folder 16)
    - Farm Bureau (Folder 17)
    - Farm Credit Administration (Folder 18)
    - Farnham's Printing and Stationery Company (Folder 19)
    - Fasanko Motor Sales (Folder 20)
    - Feemster, Ida (Folder 21)
    - Ferguson, M. H., Mrs. (Folder 22)
    - Football tickets, 1939 (Folder 23)
    - Frederickson, Paul (Folder 24)
    - Friedell, William (Folder 25)
    - G unsorted (Folder 26)
    - Galarneault, John T. (Folder 27)
    - Galbraith, Charles W. (Folder 28)
    - P. J. Gallagher & Sons (Folder 29)
    - Gallup Civil Rights Committee (Folder 30)
    - Gangloff, Fred (Folder 31)
    - Gannett, Frank E. (Folder 32)
    - Garvey, M. J. (Folder 33)
    - M. M. Gasser Company (Folder 34)
    - Gay, Frank A., Mrs. (Folder 35)
    - Geanakopolos, James A. (Folder 36)
    - General Drivers Union (Folder 37)
    - Gergely, Wilhelm, Mr. and Mrs. (Folder 38)
    - Giberton, Adrian (Folder 39)
    - Gilbertson, Gilbert G. (Box 183., Folder 1)
    - Gilchrist, Fred C. (Folder 2)
    - Gilleckson, H. E. (Folder 3)
    - Gillilland, Lillian, 1933, 1937-1940 (Folder 4)
    - Gross, Marion (Folder 5)
    - Gudes (Folder 6)
    - H unsorted (Folder 7)
    - Harris & Ewing (Folder 8)
    - Hauenstein & Burmeister (Folder 9)
    - Hawlish, Phyllis (Folder 10)
    - Hawkinson, Robert E. (Folder 11)
    - Hawley Radio, Inc. (Folder 12)
    - Hecht Company (Folder 13)
    - Hobbs, Donald (Folder 14)
    - Hoeppel, Charles J. (Folder 15)
    - Hoen, S. C. (Folder 16)
    - Hoffman, Frances, Mrs. (Folder 17)
    - Holt Motor Company (Folder 18)
    - Insurance (Folder 19)
    - Income
      - 1937 (Folder 20)
      - 1938 (Folder 21)
      - 1939 (Folder 22)
    - Independent Press Company, 1931-1938 (Folder 23)
    - Institute Cleaning Plant (Folder 24)
    - International Bank (Folder 25)
    - International News Photos (Folder 26)
    - J unsorted (Folder 27)
    - Jordan Piano Company (Folder 28)
    - K unsorted (Folder 29)
    - Kahn, A. (Folder 30)
    - Keller Studio, Beresford, S. D. (Folder 31)
    - Kelly Transfer Company, 1928-1931 (Folder 32)
    - Kunz, J. (Folder 33)
    - Kunz Oil Company (Folder 34)
    - L unsorted (Box 184., Folder 1)
    - Lindgren, John U. (Folder 2)
    - Logan, W. J. (Folder 3)
    - Lohmann, Lewis E. (Folder 4)
    - Lohmar, R. A. (Folder 5)
    - Loughlin, John (Folder 6)
    - Lucas, Cottrell (Folder 7)
    - Luczak, Peter (Folder 8)
    - Lundeen, Lorraine (Folder 9)
    - M unsorted (Folder 10)
    - Marquette National Bank
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Statements, 1932-1937 (Folder 12)
    - Masonic Lodge No. 19 (Folder 13)
    - Massopust, A. H. (Folder 14)
    - Matheson, Kenneth, Mrs. (Hattie) (Folder 15)
    - Menzel & Company (Folder 16)
    - Miller, Emma D., 1930-1940 (Folder 17)
    - Moffett Studio, Inc. (Folder 18)
    - Murray & Company, Glenn R. (Folder 19)
    - N unsorted (Folder 20)
    - National Recording Studio (Folder 21)
    - Ninth Street Garage, 1925-1938 (Folder 22)
    - Noble, Selma, Mrs. (Folder 23)
    - Northwestern Bell Telephone Company (Folder 24)
    - O unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Office help, Extra, 1930-1937 (Folder 26)
    - Oswald & Winston (Folder 27)
    - P unsorted (Folder 28)
    - Parkway Cleaners & Dyers (Folder 29)
    - Peacock, C. D. (Folder 30)
    - Potomac Electric Company (Box 185., Folder 1)
    - Pruitt, Lancefred B. (Folder 2)
    - Pure Food Stores (Folder 3)
    - Putnam's Sons (Folder 4)
    - R unsorted (Folder 5)
    - Radio (Folder 6)
    - Raleigh Haberdasher (Folder 7)
    - Rand McNally & Company (Folder 8)
    - Reedholm, Mildred (Folder 9)
    - Reiter, Julius J. (Folder 10)
    - Residences (Folder 11)
    - Ritchie, Ethel M., Mrs. (Folder 12)
    - Rosehill Nurseries (Folder 13)
    - Royal Typewriter Company (Folder 14)
    - Rydell, A. T. (Folder 15)
    - S unsorted (Folder 16)
    - Security Mutual Life Insurance Company (Brown Agency) (Folder 17)
    - Senate restaurant (Folder 18)
    - Shellman, Charles H. (Folder 19)
    - Sloan, Charles H. (Folder 20)
    - Somdal, Ida (Folder 21)
    - Sorenson, Chris D. (Folder 22)
    - Spongberg, Ernest A. (Folder 23)
    - Stationery room (Folder 24)
    - Stern, Robert (Folder 25)
    - Stevens & Company (Folder 26)
    - Strahon Transfer and Storage (Folder 27)
    - Strand, Caroline (Folder 28)
    - Swedish American Biographical Society (Folder 29)
    - Swenson, C. O., Mrs. (Folder 30)
    - T unsorted (Folder 31)
    - Taxes
      - Money and credits, 1932-1936 (Folder 32)
      - Personal property
        - 1927-1928 (Folder 33)
        - 1932 (Folder 34)
        - 1934-1936 (Folder 35)
        - Office (Folder 36)
        - Residence (Folder 37)
      - State income, 1933-1936 (Folder 38)
    - Templin, Ann (Folder 39)
    - Templin, Emma (Folder 40)
    - Templin, Helen (Folder 41)
    - Thompson's Dairy (Folder 42)
    - Thorpe Brothers (Folder 43)
    - Tolson Tree Experts and Landscape Contractors (Folder 44)
    - United Spanish War Veterans (Box 186., Folder 1)
    - W unsorted (Folder 2)
    - Warner Hardware Company (Folder 3)
    - Washington Gas and Light Company (Folder 4)
    - Weadon, Mason (Folder 5)
    - Wells, Amos, 1928, 1935-1936 (Folder 6)
    - Wesley Temple Building Office (Folder 7)
    - Whittle, H. F. (Folder 8)
    - Who's Who in America (Folder 9)
    - Widen, Robert and Donald (Folder 10)
    - Widen, W. P. (Folder 11)
    - Wiley, John & Sons (Folder 12)
    - Woodward & Lathrop (Folder 13)
    - Z unsorted (Folder 14)
  - 1936-1940. Campaign, constituent and family mail arranged alphabetically
    - A unsorted - American League for Peace and Democracy (Box 187., Folder 1-28)
    - American Legion - Bennett, James R. (Box 188., Folder 1-40)
    - American Youth Congress (Folder 3)
    - Benson, Elmer A. - Business Men's Conference (Box 189., Folder 1-53)
    - C unsorted - Civil War Veterans Association (Box 190., Folder 1-30)
    - Carleton College (Folder 6)
    - Christgau, Victor (Folder 24-25)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps - Congressional Record Office (Box 191., Folder 1-23)
    - Classmates of E. Lundeen (Folder 4)
    - A. E. Conrad Company - Densmore, Frances (Box 192., Folder 1-38)
    - Corneaby, Edward (Folder 6)
    - Davis, Tom (Folder 30)
    - DePonti, Albert - Federal Land Bank (Box 193., Folder 1-37)
    - Federal Power Commission - Hannevig, Christoffer (Box 194., Folder 1-56)
    - Gross, Marion (Folder 40)
    - Hanratty, James, Mrs. - Independent Merchants Broadcasting Corporation (Box 195., Folder 1-52)
    - Hawlish, Phyllis (Folder 19)
    - Indian affairs - Justice Department, U. S. (Box 196., Folder 1-42)
    - K unsorted - League of Women Voters (Box 197., Folder 1-51)
    - Leech, Frank - McCullough, Mr. and Mrs. W. (Box 198., Folder 1-39)
    - Lundeen, David (Folder 23)
    - Lundeen, Ernest (Folder 24)
    - Lundeen, Ernest Ward (Folder 25)
    - Lundeen, Joan (Folder 26)
    - Lundeen, Joel (Folder 27)
    - Lundeen, Norma Ward (Folder 28)
    - McDowell, Marvin - Minneapolis, Minnesota (Box 199., Folder 1-46)
    - Minneapolis & St. Louis Railroad - Mullane, Margaret L. (Box 200., Folder 1-32)
    - Moe, Henry Allen (Folder 21)
    - Mulligan, James, Mr. and Mrs. - Petitions, 1943 (Box 201., Folder 1-44)
    - Petitions, 1937 - Star Route carriers (Box 202., Folder 1-35)
    - State Department - Treasury Department (Box 203., Folder 1-42)
    - Tree planting - White House (Box 204., Folder 1-45)
    - Wick, S. S. - Works Progress Administration (Box 205., Folder 1-16)
    - Workers Alliance (Minnesota) (Folder 11)
    - Works Progress Administration - Zielsdorg, Otto (Box 206., Folder 1-15)
  - 1937-1940. Constituent mail, congressional office business and letters to organizations arranged alphabetically
    - A personal (Box 207., Folder 1)
    - A unsorted (Folder 2)
    - Aeschilman, William, Mrs. (Folder 3)
    - Andreen, Florence (Folder 4)
    - Ayshford, Stuart (Folder 5)
    - B personal (Folder 6)
    - B unsorted (Folder 7)
    - Battery Park Market (Folder 8)
    - Bell, Frank T. (Folder 9)
    - Bostwick, C. L. (Folder 10)
    - Byerhoff, W. G. (Folder 11)
    - C personal (Folder 12)
    - C unsorted (Folder 13)
    - Carleton, Doris Grace (Folder 14)
    - Carleton College (Ernest Ward Lundeen, 1939-1941) (Folder 15)
    - Congressional Club (Folder 16)
    - Constituents (Folder 17)
    - Cook books sent (Folder 18)
    - D personal (Folder 19)
    - D unsorted (Folder 20)
    - Dahlberg, Bror G. (Folder 21)
    - Devaney, John P. (Folder 22)
    - Donnelly, Ignatius (Folder 23)
    - E personal (Folder 24)
    - F unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Foshay-Henly case (Folder 26)
    - G personal (Folder 27)
    - G unsorted (Folder 28)
    - Garfinckel and Company (Folder 29)
    - Goodyear, Evelyn (Folder 30)
    - Gray, John H. (Folder 31)
    - H personal (Box 208., Folder 1)
    - H unsorted (Folder 2)
    - Hansen, Ferdinand (Folder 3)
    - Harris, Ned Brunson (Folder 4)
    - Hawaiian trip expenses (Folder 5)
    - Hecht Company (Folder 6)
    - Hoeppel, John H. (Folder 7)
    - Holmes, Emil E. (Folder 8)
    - Horrigan, Alvilde (Folder 9)
    - Hotels (Folder 10)
    - Hunter, Croil (Folder 11)
    - I personal (Folder 12)
    - I unsorted (Folder 13)
    - Insurance (Folder 14)
    - Interstate Power Company (Folder 15)
    - J personal (Folder 16)
    - J unsorted (Folder 17)
    - Jelleff Incorporated (Folder 18)
    - Johannes, Michael J. (Folder 19)
    - Johnson, J. Fred (Folder 20)
    - Jordan, Mary W. and M. A. (Folder 21)
    - K personal (Folder 22)
    - K unsorted (Folder 23)
    - Kayser, Ida, Mrs. (Folder 24)
    - Kipp, R. H. (Folder 25)
    - Kornmann, Conrad (Folder 26)
    - L personal (Folder 27)
    - Lee, Edward and Emma (Folder 28)
    - Linden, Phil (Folder 29)
    - Los Angeles (Folder 30)
    - Lundeen, David
      - General (Folder 31)
      - Disbarment (Folder 32)
    - Lundeen, Ernest (Box 209., Folder 1)
    - Lundeen, Ernest Ward (Folder 2)
    - Lundeen, Joan (Folder 3)
    - Lundeen, Joel and Esther (Folder 4)
    - Lundeen, Lorraine (Folder 5)
    - Lundien, Fern Woodard, Mrs. (Folder 6)
    - Lundin, Fred (Folder 7)
    - Lundquist, Marguerite (Folder 8)
    - M personal (Folder 9)
    - M unsorted (Folder 10)
    - McCarthy, Sam R. (Folder 11)
    - MacLean, E. L. (Folder 12)
    - Maid service (Folder 13)
    - Matheson, John (Folder 14)
    - Matheson, Ken, Hattie and Jane (Folder 15)
    - Matheson, Rod and Bertha (Folder 16)
    - Matheson, William J. and Belle (Folder 17)
    - Mileage (Folder 18)
    - Miller, Troy S. and Helen (Folder 19)
    - Minnesota State Society of Washington, D. C. (Folder 20)
    - Minnetonka Lake (water level) (Folder 21)
    - Morton Museum and House, John (Folder 22)
    - Mottoes (Folder 23)
    - Mudge, Rollo and Myrtle (Folder 24)
    - N unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Names and addresses (Box 210., Folder 1)
    - National Committee to Uphold Constitutional Government (Folder 2)
    - National Council for Prevention of War (Folder 3)
    - National Emergency Council (Folder 4)
    - National Farmers Bank of Owatonna (Folder 5)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees (Folder 6)
    - National Grange (Folder 7)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Folder 8)
    - National Rifle Association (Folder 9)
    - National Rivers and Harbors Congress (Folder 10)
    - National Union for Social Justice (Folder 11)
    - National Weeklies, Inc. (Folder 12)
    - National Woman's Party (Folder 13)
    - National Youth Administration (Folder 14)
    - Nationalities
      - Jewish (Folder 15)
      - German (Folder 16)
      - Norwegian (Folder 17)
      - Polish (Folder 18)
      - Scandinavian (Folder 19)
    - Navy Department (Folder 20)
    - Negro organizations (Folder 21)
    - Nelson, Adelbert L. (Folder 22)
    - Nelson, Arthur (Folder 23)
    - Nelson, Oscar L. (Folder 24)
    - Nelson, S. J. (Folder 25)
    - Nelson, Thomas (Folder 26)
    - Newburgh, John (Folder 27)
    - New England Furniture Company (Folder 28)
    - New York City. Congressional visit, 1937 (Folder 29)
    - Nickels and Smith Company (Folder 30)
    - Nigg, Herman (Folder 31)
    - Norby, Albert H. (Folder 32)
    - Norby Department Store (Folder 33)
    - Nordmarken, O. G. (Folder 34)
    - Nordstrom, Richard C. (Folder 35)
    - Norling, Sven A. (Folder 36)
    - Norman, Henry (Folder 37)
    - Northby, Paul (Folder 38)
    - Northern Farmers Cooperative (Folder 39)
    - Northland Ski Manufacturing Company (Folder 40)
    - Northwest Creamery Owners Association (Folder 41)
    - Northwest Shippers Advisory Board (Folder 42)
    - Northwestern Forwarding Company (Folder 43)
    - Northwestern Marble Corporation (Folder 44)
    - Norton, E. V. (Folder 45)
    - Neumeier, Fritz (Folder 46)
    - Nye, Gerald (Folder 47)
    - O personal (Folder 48)
    - O unsorted (Folder 49)
    - Oakleaf, S., Mrs. (Folder 50)
    - Oberg, A. C. and Stella (Folder 51)
    - O'Brien, James T. (Folder 52)
    - O'Brien, Robert William (Folder 53)
    - O'Brien, Thomas (Box 211., Folder 1)
    - Occhinnero, George (Folder 2)
    - Odegard, Enbret (Folder 3)
    - Office help (Folder 4)
    - Office space, Minneapolis (Folder 5)
    - Okes Construction Company (Folder 6)
    - O'Leary, C. P. (Folder 7)
    - Oleson, Ole P. (Folder 8)
    - Olsen, Selma (Folder 9)
    - Olson, Albert (Folder 10)
    - Olson, John O. (Folder 11)
    - P personal (Folder 12)
    - P unsorted (Folder 13)
    - Pearson, Alice (Folder 14)
    - Peerage Press (Folder 15)
    - Pejsah, Rozin (Folder 16)
    - Peterson, Harry H. (Folder 17)
    - Pierz Cooperative Association (Folder 18)
    - Pitera, Alfredo (Folder 19)
    - Pittman, Joseph (Folder 20)
    - Poole, Alvin (Folder 21)
    - Popham, N. A. (Folder 22)
    - Posen, Joseph (Folder 23)
    - Posey, George A. (Folder 24)
    - Positions (correspondence from people seeking jobs)
      - General (Folder 25)
      - B (Folder 26)
      - C (Folder 27)
      - D (Folder 28)
      - E (Folder 29)
      - G (Folder 30)
      - H (Folder 31)
      - J (Folder 32)
      - K (Folder 33)
      - L (Folder 34)
      - M (Box 212., Folder 1)
      - O (Folder 2)
      - P (Folder 3)
      - R (Folder 4)
      - S (Folder 5)
      - T (Folder 6)
      - W (Folder 7)
    - Positions (jobs secured)
      - Delin, Bertha (Folder 8)
      - Johnson, Harriet (Folder 9)
      - Lundeen, Joel (Folder 10)
      - McQuat, Raymond A. (Folder 11)
      - Widen, Ed (Folder 12)
    - Post Office Department
      - General (Folder 13)
      - Afton (Folder 14)
      - Aitkin (Folder 15)
      - Albany (Folder 16)
      - Alberta (Folder 17)
      - Alborn (Folder 18)
      - Allen Junction (Folder 19)
      - Angora (Folder 20)
      - Anoka (Folder 21)
      - Audubon (Folder 22)
      - Barnum (Folder 23)
      - Baudette (Folder 24)
      - Bovey (Folder 25)
      - Braham (Folder 26)
      - Butterfield (Folder 27)
      - Cambridge (Folder 28)
      - Cannon Falls (Folder 29)
      - Cedar (Folder 30)
      - Centerville (Folder 31)
      - Cloquet (Folder 32)
      - Constance (Folder 33)
      - Cook (Folder 34)
      - Crystal (Folder 35)
      - Currie (Folder 36)
      - Dassel (Box 213., Folder 1)
      - Deer River (Folder 2)
      - Duluth (Folder 3)
      - Dundas (Folder 4)
      - Echo (Folder 5)
      - Edgerton (Folder 6)
      - Finlayson (Folder 7)
      - Forest Lake (Folder 8)
      - Fosston (Folder 9)
      - Fox (Folder 10)
      - Garden City (Folder 11)
      - Garfield (Folder 12)
      - Glencoe (Folder 13)
      - Glenwood (Folder 14)
      - Golden Valley (Folder 15)
      - Grandy (Folder 16)
      - Gully (Folder 17)
      - Halma (Folder 18)
      - Hitterdahl (Folder 19)
      - Holdingford (Folder 20)
      - Hutchinson (Folder 21)
      - Island Park (Folder 22)
      - Jasper (Folder 23)
      - Kelsey (Folder 24)
      - Little Falls (Folder 25)
      - Lockhart (Folder 26)
      - Long Prairie (Folder 27)
      - Lynd (Folder 28)
      - Madison (Folder 29)
      - Magnolia (Folder 30)
      - Malmo (Folder 31)
      - Maple Lake (Folder 32)
      - Marshall (Folder 33)
      - Minneapolis (Folder 34)
      - Moose Lake (Folder 35)
      - Morris (Folder 36)
      - New Ulm (Folder 37)
      - Nicollet (Folder 38)
      - North Redwood (Folder 39)
      - Oxboro (Folder 40)
      - Palisade (Folder 41)
      - Paynesville (Folder 42)
      - Pine City (Folder 43)